LAUGHING MAN FANSUBS
Angels and demons were circling over me,
Crossing a brambly path of stars and milky ways.
Not knowing happiness is the only one,
The one who could not understand its call.
The flow may swallow you. The flow may swallow you
Flying in glory, Flying in glory
I am calling, calling now.
Spirits rise and falling.
To be with you longer
Calling, calling...
in the depth of longing
To be with you longer...
The flow may swallow you, flying in glory
I just returned to duty.
I thought that you didn't have permission
to be released from the hospital.
Please stop that.
I can't be the only one
bedridden at a time like this.
I'm the one who called Togusa back.
The necessary documents have been assembled.
I will have you go with me to
the Prime Minister's residence.
Roger.
Are you really okay?
You're not fully healed yet, are you?
Leave it to me.
After all, it was Togusa who made
the first connection in the case.
The Sun Sets
on an
Isolated Fortress
Chief.
What is it?
We have an emergency transmission
from the Minister of the interior.
All right, put it through.
Aramaki-kun, it's me.
Are you watching channel W-3?
No.
Then, please look at it now.
Members of Public Safety's Section 9, an
organisation under the Ministry of the Interior,
The truth behind the laughing man case?
Was the Ministry of the Interior's Public Safety Organisation involved in Mr Serano's Kidnapping?
is now thought to have been involved in the attempted
kidnapping of Serano Genomix's president, Mr. Earnest Serano.
Section 9, an organisation within the Ministry of the Interior,
is recognised as an international rescue unit.
Niihama Prefecture, Niihama City
Public Safety Headquarters
Was the Ministry of the Interior's
Public Safety Organisation
involved in Mr Serano's Kidnapping?
However, its excessive intelligence activities and
use of force have been cause for much concern.
From this case, there is a high possibility that Section 9 has been
involved in the chain of events of the Laughing Man Case in 2024...
Major...!
I am attending an emergency cabinet meeting.
What an unnecessary hassle.
You should come here immediately as well.
And it would be best for you to come up
with answers while you're on your way.
Does this mean that information
was leaked beforehand, then?
Don't panic. This merely means that
our plan has been set into motion.
We will proceed to the Prime
Minister's residence as planned.
Major.
Yes?
Determine where the leak occurred.
Roger.
With this, we will now need to conduct a sweeping
review regarding the need for Section 9.
Social unrest, which has been
steadily increasing after Section
9's existence was exposed, has
gone beyond the critical point.
Prime Minister, while Public Safety officially lies
under the Ministry of the Interior's jurisdiction,
I have heard that there are certain instances
in which you can issue direct orders as well.
Well, such things have been
known to happen before, but...
Well, it is also true that Section 9 is quite valuable
as an international rescue unit with combat experience.
How easily you say such things when you didn't
even know what was happening in your own turf.
Section 9 is an assassins group. In
the war's aftermath, its creation
was approved without debate based on
the then Prime Minister's orders.
Considering the Article 9 issue regarding our Self Defence Forces, for which no
resolution is yet in sight, public opinion is delicately balanced at the moment.
In any case, this discussion will not make any
headway until the Chief of Section 9 arrives.
What?
Excuse me, everyone. I will return momentarily.
What is this all about?
I am in a difficult situation thanks to this case.
You will not be able to avoid being
summoned to testify under oath, either.
I am sure you can imagine how dangerous
it is for me to meet you right now.
I am aware of that.
However... please see this.
What is it?
Highly classified documents on Secretary
General Yakushima that are of grave import.
I wonder if we made it in time for the big bust.
Who else has seen this cash flow
and understand its implications?
You, who has just read the dossier; Mr.
Serano, who has hardened
his resolve to accuse the Secretary
General; and my subordinates.
I see. I understand.
I will deal with Mr. Yakushima
at the appropriate time.
However, this is a key time
before the Lower House elections.
I would like to let the people and
the media have the limelight.
If we are to oust someone as
prominent as Yakushima-San,
a substantial degree of sacrifice
on our part can not be avoided.
I fail to grasp exactly what you mean by that.
I am referring to the enactment of
the Special Forces Control Bill.
Are you telling me to toss
Section 9 out the window?
I did not say that.
Wait a minute, please!
My trust in my subordinates, whose faith in
me never wavers under any circumstances...
that faith encompasses the totality of the
"wealth" that I've strived to create!
And you're trying to...?
It appears that the time has
come to utilise that wealth.
I will make the necessary preparations.
You will summon your subordinates.
Don't worry. As long as you are here,
you'll be able to restructure Section 9.
Go to the Ministry of Justice.
Yes, sir.
Major, it's me.
Were you able to persuade the Prime Minister?
Order all members to Section 9.
Any other orders?
Don't die.
Survive, no matter what.
The enemy has nine sentient tanks.
Teams 3 and 4, drop down to the
heliport and infiltrate the hangar.
Our highest priority is to neutralise those tanks!
Teams 5 and 6, secure the seven main members ASAP!
We will seize control of the entire facility.
Upon infiltration, set your
cyberbrain to autistic mode.
The enemy is adept at information warfare.
We will overtake them by force.
Chief...
They're following us.
We'll shake them off.
Chief!
We have come to get you.
You still have something you must do.
To make all the necessary arrangements
in this short a time period...
The Prime Minister is indeed competent.
They must be attempting to
neutralise Section 9 by now.
What did you say...?!
Take him.
Yes, sir!
Chief, what is going on?
Please explain!
Chief!
Chief!!!
Doesn't something feel different about this place?
Plus, this call is kind of weird, too...
I don't have time to explain
the situation right now.
For now, carry out my orders
without asking questions.
Bring six backup cybernetic bodies
to the command centre ASAP.
Could it be that...
Hurry.
Major, what is this all about?
I will give you these "seeds".
After you get out of here, leak the information
inside the seeds to the media and let them sprout.
Public support will be crucial if we
are to oust the Secretary General.
Brought them.
I received an encrypted
transmission from the Chief.
I predict that a special op unit from the military
will soon arrive to neutralise this facility.
As I'd thought, the Special
Forces Control Bill was invoked.
By the time that military force is
authorizes through an emergency
cabinet meeting, everything will
have already been taken care of...
it's nothing new.
They're here.
After we buy as much time as we can,
we'll shut this place down!
We've secured the hangar!
No sign of sentient tanks!
Beware of ambush!
Colonel, a terminal has a record stating that
the sentient tanks were sent to the labs!
Dammit! The command's
intelligence is always like this.
Cut the chatter!
The situation is subject to change in an instant.
Take all possibilities into
consideration and deploy the teams!
Whoo, here they come!
Let's go!
Ishikawa, activate the sprinklers!
No effect.
It's just water.
Team 2, provide backup support!
Use that reinforced exoskeleton to overwhelm them!
We'll retreat.
We can't buy any time against that exoskeleton
no matter how much we fire at it!
Where the hell is that unit from?
They're formidable.
Umibouzu means
"sea monk" or "sea priest",
a supernatural creature
from Japanese folklore
They're the Umibouzu.
The Umibouzu?!
Yeah.
They took part in the
Nemuro Recapture Operation.
They're famous in the underground.
Since they're not supposed to exist,
they don't have an official name.
It's about time to end this.
We're getting out of here.
Give me a status report!
Expedite recovery of casualties!
it appears that Section 9
members committed suicide.
Account for the possibility that it is a subterfuge
to make it look as if they committed suicide.
Don't let your guard down!
Continue with the search!
Roger!
Oh, jeez, look at you!
Don't spill your tea!
Tachikoma-Chan really tries a lot.
It's really industrious and became
friends with everyone right away.
Yes, it's really a big help...
but isn't it actually a reject
from some organisation?
I wonder if they have more like it...
True, true...
But, I wonder what that
robot's original purpose was.
Hey, hey. There's the news!
We apologise for interrupting the current program,
Let's all watch TV!
but we will now report and a Section 9 update.
Oh?
In the emergency cabinet meeting, in
which Section 9 was requested to disarm,
Ministry of the Interior - Anti-terrorism unit
Clash with the Military upon refusal to comply with the Special Forces Control Bill  /Niihama
enforcement of the Special Forces Control Bill was
approved with the possibility of using military force.
However, Section 9 refuses to comply despite repeated
warnings and now seems prepared to respond with force.
A military special ops unit now appears to have
begun an assault on Section 9's headquarters.
Now for live coverage from the scene.
This is... about Section 9!
The military special ops unit just landed on the
building where Section 9 is headquartered...
We don't seem to have pursuers thus far.
We didn't buy that much time.
After all, none of the cyberbrains had heavy use.
Well? What are we going to do now?
The Chief told me not to die and to survive.
I agree with him.
From here on, we will split into
three groups and divide pursuit.
Afterward, each of you will take off
and conceal yourselves in the city.
As of today, Public Safety Section 9 is disbanded.
That is all.
There is heavy damage, but it appears that
these are the remains of the six members.
We are currently analysing the
extent of cyberbrain usage.
Before the analysis results
come through, call Team 5.
Assume subterfuge and block all possible routes such as
the elevator shafts, exhaust outlets, and sewage systems.
Go first.
No, you're going first.
When the pursuit catches up, my
body will block the passageway.
And what if the enemy sets on ambush of the exit?
Where will you be able to run if
I'm in front and block the exit?
So, Section 9 is finally gone.
All that we've worked hard to
create is now cast to the wind.
Do you think so?
It was nice that we had lavish access to the
top-notch maintenance and cutting edge equipment,
but that was all it was.
We just need to find a new sponsor.
Or is there something else?
Are you sentimentally attached there, Batou?
Now that you mention it, no.
Well, if I did have any, only memories, I guess.
Memories?
How sentimental of you.
Oh yeah, where is the watch that you always wear?
I left it at my bedside in the
safe house, today of all days.
Since Section 9 was hit, I'm
sure apartment was seized, too.
Are you okay with that?
Wasn't that wristwatch a present you received when
you stopped having to re size your cybernetic body?
Not that I know who gave it to you, of course...
You knew about that?
But don't get me wrong.
I wasn't wearing it out of sentimental value.
Weren't you insisting on a female
body type because you wanted
to have a wrist that would be
slim enough to wear that watch?
You can change cyberbrains
and cybernetic bodies, sure;
but there are some things that
can't be changed, aren't there?
What are you getting so fired up about?
I've been changing cyberbrains and cybernetic
bodies to adapt to the relevant circumstances.
If so, then I will change
memories, too, that's all.
Our idle chatter is finished.
After we get out of here, we can
never contact each other again.
Even if we are to meet again,
I may not be who I am now.
You should also prioritise
your own survival, Batou.
Niihama Prefectural Police -- Niihama Police Department
As I've already said many times
before, that is not true.
Then, why was Section 9 agent
disguised as the Laughing Man
and was in contact with the President?
Well, that's because...
Because what?
Besides, Section 9 didn't even exist six years ago!
How can it be involved in the Laughing Man Case?
As if you people aren't
specialists at falsifying data.
Stop this already.
Six years ago, I was a detective
at police headquarters, too.
All right, let's start again,
all the way from the beginning.
Let's part our ways here.
Right.
I came instead of the Major.
Do you have the usual drink?
I'm sorry... I have loans from
my cybernetic body, so...
If you don't want to die, don't struggle.
They've even found out about this place already...?
I don't usually accept jobs
from anyone else but her,
but since it's an emergency, I guess
I'll make a special exception.
Okay!
Oh?
The war is getting worse...
Everyone...
What is this about?
Why are you ordering the armour
suits unit to withdraw?
They are not opponents who can be defeated
unless we expend all possible means to do so!
We have confirmed neutralization.
It would not be wise for us to take further
conspicuous actions at this point in time.
Understood.
Leave two armors suit units behind
and have all the others withdraw.
Roger.
However...
We were not ordered to withdraw all the units.
Go!
Yes, sir!
Well, it's my life after all.
It means I can spend it however I wish.
She's so cold and human
It's something humans do
She stays so cold in her soul, she's so number 9
She's incredible math
Just incredible math
And is she really human?
She says there's something new
But wake a lithium flower, just about to bloom
I smell lithium now
Smelling lithium now
How... is she what she doesn't say
She doesn't say
How is she when she doesn't suffer
I wonder what she does when she wakes up
When she wakes up